<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<layout
    xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <androidx.coordinatorlayout.widget.CoordinatorLayout
        xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        android:background="@color/cardview_light_background">

        <androidx.core.widget.NestedScrollView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="match_parent">

            <LinearLayout
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:orientation="vertical">

                <androidx.cardview.widget.CardView
                    android:layout_width="match_parent"
                    android:layout_height="280dp"
                    app:cardCornerRadius="0dp">

                    <RelativeLayout
                        android:layout_width="match_parent"
                        android:layout_height="match_parent">

                        <ImageView
                            android:id="@+id/image"
                            android:layout_width="match_parent"
                            android:layout_height="match_parent"
                            android:src="@drawable/pizza_margarita"
                            android:scaleType="fitXY"/>

                        <View
                            android:id="@+id/anchorButton"
                            android:layout_alignParentBottom="true"
                            android:layout_width="match_parent"
                            android:layout_height="14dp"/>

                    </RelativeLayout>

                </androidx.cardview.widget.CardView>

                <RelativeLayout
                    android:layout_width="match_parent"
                    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                    android:layout_marginTop="10dp">

                    <TextView
                        android:id="@+id/title"
                        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                        android:layout_alignParentStart="true"
                        android:paddingStart="8dp"
                        android:paddingTop="8dp"
                        android:text="Pizza Margarita"
                        android:fontFamily="@font/belmonte"
                        android:textColor="@color/colorPrimary"
                        android:textSize="20sp"
                        android:textStyle="bold"
                        android:paddingLeft="8dp"
                        android:layout_alignParentLeft="true"/>

                    <TextView
                        android:id="@+id/category"
                        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                        android:layout_alignParentStart="true"
                        android:layout_below="@+id/title"
                        android:paddingBottom="8dp"
                        android:paddingStart="8dp"
                        android:text="Women, Dress, Summer"
                        android:textColor="@color/darkGrey"
                        android:textSize="12sp"
                        android:paddingLeft="8dp"
                        android:layout_alignParentLeft="true"/>

                    <TextView
                        android:id="@+id/price"
                        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                        android:layout_alignParentEnd="true"
                        android:layout_centerVertical="true"
                        android:paddingEnd="8dp"
                        android:text="145 calorias"
                        android:fontFamily="@font/belmonte"
                        android:textColor="@color/cardview_dark_background"
                        android:textSize="14sp"
                        android:textStyle="bold"
                        android:paddingRight="8dp"
                        android:layout_alignParentRight="true"/>

                    <RatingBar
                        android:id="@+id/ratingBar"
                        style="@style/Widget.AppCompat.RatingBar.Small"
                        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                        android:layout_below="@+id/category"
                        android:layout_marginBottom="8dp"
                        android:layout_marginStart="8dp"
                        android:rating="4"
                        android:layout_marginLeft="8dp"/>

                </RelativeLayout>

                <View
                    android:layout_width="match_parent"
                    android:layout_height="2dp"
                    android:background="@color/darkGrey" />

                <RelativeLayout
                    android:layout_width="match_parent"
                    android:layout_height="wrap_content">

                    <LinearLayout
                        android:layout_width="match_parent"
                        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                        android:layout_alignParentBottom="true"
                        android:animateLayoutChanges="true"
                        android:orientation="vertical">

                        <RelativeLayout
                            android:layout_width="match_parent"
                            android:layout_height="wrap_content">

                            <TextView
                                android:id="@+id/descriptionTitle"
                                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                                android:layout_alignParentStart="true"
                                android:paddingBottom="4dp"
                                android:paddingEnd="8dp"
                                android:paddingStart="8dp"
                                android:paddingTop="8dp"
                                android:text="DESCRIPTION"
                                android:textStyle="bold"
                                android:layout_alignParentLeft="true"/>

                        </RelativeLayout>

                        <TextView
                            android:id="@+id/description"
                            android:layout_width="match_parent"
                            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                            android:paddingBottom="8dp"
                            android:paddingEnd="8dp"
                            android:paddingStart="8dp"
                            android:text="I believe this is the most often missed issue as it doesn't appear in most other answers nor examples. The answer above mentions both appcompat and design, so is technically more correct, but I bet most people wouldn't get this far if appcompat were missing. The actual version of design doesn't matter, so feel free to use a newer one if your Android Studio has a newer one already installedI believe this is the most often missed issue as it doesn't appear in most other answers nor examples. The answer above mentions both appcompat and design, so is technically more correct, but I bet most people wouldn't get this far if appcompat were missing. The actual version of design doesn't matter, so feel free to use a newer one if your Android Studio has a newer one already installed. I believe this is the most often missed issue as it doesn't appear in most other answers nor examples. The answer above mentions both appcompat and design, so is technically more correct, but I bet most people wouldn't get this far if appcompat were missing. The actual version of design doesn't matter, so feel free to use a newer one if your Android Studio has a newer one already installedI believe this is the most often missed issue as it doesn't appear in most other answers nor examples. The answer above mentions both appcompat and design, so is technically more correct, but I bet most people wouldn't get this far if appcompat were missing. The actual version of design doesn't matter, so feel free to use a newer one if your Android Studio has a newer one already installed. I believe this is the most often missed issue as it doesn't appear in most other answers nor examples. The answer above mentions both appcompat and design, so is technically more correct, but I bet most people wouldn't get this far if appcompat were missing. The actual version of design doesn't matter, so feel free to use a newer one if your Android Studio has a newer one already installedI believe this is the most often missed issue as it doesn't appear in most other answers nor examples. The answer above mentions both appcompat and design, so is technically more correct, but I bet most people wouldn't get this far if appcompat were missing. The actual version of design doesn't matter, so feel free to use a newer one if your Android Studio has a newer one already installed.I believe this is the most often missed issue as it doesn't appear in most other answers nor examples. The answer above mentions both appcompat and design, so is technically more correct, but I bet most people wouldn't get this far if appcompat were missing. The actual version of design doesn't matter, so feel free to use a newer one if your Android Studio has a newer one already installedI believe this is the most often missed issue as it doesn't appear in most other answers nor examples. The answer above mentions both appcompat and design, so is technically more correct, but I bet most people wouldn't get this far if appcompat were missing. The actual version of design doesn't matter, so feel free to use a newer one if your Android Studio has a newer one already installed" />

                    </LinearLayout>

                </RelativeLayout>

            </LinearLayout>

        </androidx.core.widget.NestedScrollView>

    </androidx.coordinatorlayout.widget.CoordinatorLayout>
</layout>
